Well if I don't
Bueno si no
die if I don't die let's go
muero si no muero vamos a
[Music] let's
[Música]
see how
ver vamos a ver cómo lo lleva
Loli does and I know where I can put a sign for you
Loli y sé dónde te puedo poner cartelito
to put my name vitum My name with
para poner mi nombre vitum Mi nombre con
the vitum that speaking of bitum visum
el vitum que que hablando de bitum visum
visum
visum
or do you want to Browse the
u quieres Navegar de forma segura en
internet safely and also access all the
internet y además acceder a todo el
content of your favorite platforms
contenido de tus plataformas favoritas
like Netflix hbo Max or Disney Plus
como Netflix hbo Max o Disney Plus
cyberghost VPN And I don't know if you
cyberghost VPN Y es que no sé si lo
know but there is content that is not available in your country
sabes pero hay contenidos que en tu país
and with this little
no están disponibles y con este
trick you can access all the
truquillo puedes acceder a todo el
content wherever you are I don't know if you
contenido estés donde estés no sé si
know what a VPN is but it's an
sabes lo que es una VPN pero es una
extension that you put on your internet with
extensión que le pones a tu internet con
which it masks the IP and apart from
la que enmascara la IP y aparte de
browsing completely safely and anonymously
Navegar completamente seguro y anónimo
without anyone being able to know who you are and
sin que nadie pueda saber quién eres y
where you are It helps you access
dónde estás Te sirve para acceder a
some content that is blocked
algunos contenidos que están bloqueados
in your country there are movies and series on your
en tu país hay películas y series en tus
favorite platforms that are not
plataformas favoritas que no están
available there are television programs
disponibles hay programas de televisión
for example on mediaset content that
por ejemplo en mediaset contenidos que
if you try to watch them outside of Spain they
si los intentas ver fuera de España
have a geoblock that doesn't
tienen un geobloqueo que no te lo
allow it Well with cyberghost VPN that's
permite Pues con cyberghost VPN eso se
over Apart from being protected and
acabó Aparte de estar protegido y
browsing under the  anonymity you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet in addition you will have
planeta además tendrá tendrás privacidad
Total privacy since it keeps your connection
Total ya que mantiene tu conexión en
private and protects your data
privado y protege tus datos velocidad
Ultra fast speed to eliminate the lake in
Ultra rápida para eliminar el lago en
any online game with which you
cualquier juego online con los que
can enjoy live broadcasts without
podrás disfrutar de directos sin
interruptions and as I have already told you
interrupciones y como ya os he dicho
Freedom to access all the
Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also Take advantage of a whole 83%
quieras además Aprovecha todo un 83 por
discount using the link that I
de descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and be careful
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try cyberghost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar cyberghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced you ask for a refund and they will give you
convence pides el reembolso y y te
back the psa So don't wait any longer
devuelven la psa Así que no esperes más
to protect your connection and increase your
para proteger tu conexión y aumentar tu
internet experience run to click on the
experiencia en internet corre al click
link in the description and take advantage of
al enlace de la descripción y aprovecha
this super offer Cyber ​​goost VPN to
esta super oferta Cyber goost VPN para
browse completely free and secure we
navegar completamente libre y seguro
continue with the
seguimos con el
video Hey Javi after they have already
vídeo Oye Javi después de que ya te han
shown you that you have offered to
demostrado de que te has ofrecido a
return
devolver
Oh
Ay por
please that was that we told him not
favor eso fue eso se lo comentamos no en
live no family
directo no familia
that was a cli from the
eso fue un cli del acosador del
Wilson stalker who put a cli the famous cli
Wilson que que puso un cli el famoso cli
where where I was saying to Loli
donde donde yo le decía a Loli
Loli if you are going to cross me out in my face the
Loli si me vas a tachando en cara el
money that you've given here I'll return it to you
dinero que has dado aquí te lo devuelvo
Okay so the
Vale entonces el
stalker put the
acosador puso el
clip cutting it now we're going to see the
clip cortándolo ahora lo vamos a ver
whole clip okay it's on my Twitter
entero el clip vale está en mi Twitter
but he put the clip cutting it because It turns out that
pero puso el clip cortándolo porque
that clip Of course She
Resulta ser que ese clip Claro Ella lo
sells it as if I had gone you
vende como si yo hubiera ido lo
mentioned it at the salseria but I uploaded it
comentaste en la salsería pero lo subí
here we uploaded the extract here too
aquí lo subimos aquí el extracto también
or rather they sell it to you as if I have
o sea ellos te lo venden como que yo he
gone almost daily saying that
ido casi a diario diciendo que
offering to return all the money
ofreciéndome a devolverle todo el dinero
that she has given here look before
que ella haya dado aquí mira antes de
listening to that clown who goes like this Now
escuchar que la payasa que vay así Ahora
okay point number one that click that
vale e punto número uno ese click que
is cut okay eh that clip was in
está recortado vale eh ese clip era en
the other house I mean if you see the clip
la otra casa o sea si tú ves el clip
Also I am in the other house I mean it means
Además estoy en la otra casa o sea
that that was three years ago
quiere decir que eso hace tres años
easily okay
tranquilamente vale
eh with What with what am I going not with that
eh con Con qué a qué voy no con eso de
3 years thing What does it matter The 3 years man
los 3 años Qué importa Los 3 años hombre
well it matters that by that time
pues importa que para ese momento pues
Loli Maybe she had come in here
Loli A lo mejor había entrado aquí
four times and had donated 500 euros what
cuatro veces y había donado 500 eur qué
happened because that was one of the
es lo que pasó porque ahí fue una de las
first times that she was starting to
primeras veces que estuvo empezando a
show her paw and we found her
enseñar la patita y nos la encontramos
DIF loving me I don't remember which
DIF amándome no me acuerdo en qué caja
comment box it was if it was
de comentarios fue si fue la caja de
Enrique's comment box or I don't remember
comentarios de Enrique o no me acuerdo
who okay And then we called her
de quién vale Y entonces la la llamamos
live and I said Loli why
en directo y le dije Loli por qué me
are you slandering me I mean I don't remember what she
estás difamando O sea no me acuerdo queé
's making up but we
es lo que se está inventando pero la
caught her in a comment box
pillamos en una caja de comentario
making up something but to her face
inventándose algo pero por la cara
making up something You know about me and I said
inventándose algo Sabes de mí y le dije
What have I done to you why do you have to be out
Qué te he hecho porque tienes que estaba
there slander send me And on top of that throwing it
por ahí difam mándame Y encima echándome
in my face that I had donated I don't know what so that's
en cara que me había donado no sé qué
when I said if you're going to
entonces ahí fue cuando le dije si vas a
be out there being a pain in the ass for 500 whatever you
estar por ahí dando por culo por 500 lo
've left here in these two or
que hayas dejado aquí en estas dos o
three times I'll give it back to you okay And she on
tres veces te lo devuelvo vale Y ella en
the
la
call Sorry sorry
llamada Perdón perdón
sorry in Enrique's comment box
perdón en la caja de comentarios de
and she put you interested in a space
Enrique y te puso interesado en un space
Yes yes yes but to her face eh she got angry
Sí sí sí pero por la cara eh se enfadó
with something I said about Antonio David the
con algo que dije de Antonio David la
lady fan of Antonio David okay
señora fan de Antonio David vale
fanatic her platonic love Antonio David
fanática su amor platónico Antonio David
who called late at night
que llamaba a las tantas de la noche
so I could teach him how to put up a painting
para que le enseñara a colocar un cuadro
and then I said we said something on the
y Y entonces dije dijimos algo en el
channel about  Antonio we gave some
canal sobre Antonio avío dimos alguna
news about Antonio and she didn't
noticia sobre Antonio av que a ella no
like it and she went on space like she's
le gustaba y se puso en space como está
saying alnea to put me in a bad mood Yeah well to
diciendo alnea ponerme verde s Sí pues a
me she was talking to me because I gave her I don't know
mí que me hablaba porque le di no sé
how much money you know and here I had given
cuánto dinero sabes y aquí había dado
Well maybe 300 500 what I would have
Pues a lo mejor 300 500 los que hubiera
given at that time okay But it was
dado en ese momento vale Pero hace
a long time ago I had given very little it hadn't been
muchísimo tiempo había dado poco no se
much At that time she
había pasado mucho En aquel momento ella
started to donate more here
empezó a donar más aquí
in Marina's first time
en la primera época de
she started to donate more here in
Marina ella empezó a donar más aquí en
Marina's first time before
la primera época de Marina antes de
coming here Marina she had hardly given
venir aquí Marina ella no había dado
So I went and I said to her two
apenas Entonces yo cogí y le dije dos
filthy duros that you have given here if you are
duros guarros que has dado aquí si te
going to start putting me in a bad mood out there to
vas a poner a ponerme verde por ahí a
throw it in my face I'll give them back and
echarme en cara Te los devuelvo y coge
she answers the call lowers her ears and
ella la llamada agacha las orejitas y
says no no No man no I don't
dice que no no No hombre no yo no
need the money give it back to me I
necesito el dinero que me lo devuelvan
don't know what yes it's true I was wrong I got
no sé qué sí es verdad Me he equivocado
heated I don't know what it's worth but that's it for
me he calentado no sé qué vale pero ya
me later I mean I don't know how much
está yo ya después O sea yo no sé cuánto
that woman has given man it's not a
habrá dado esa mujer hombre no es una
figure surely significant in my
cifra seguramente significativa en mi
salary Okay but no I'm not going to  take me eh
sueldo Vale pero no no voy a [__] yo eh
now after all it's worth after
ahora después de todo vale después de
all the programs in which she has
todos los programas en los que ella haya
donated and I'm going to add up to see
donado y me voy a poner a sumar a ver
how much she has given and if it has been 2s or
cuánto ha dado ella y si han sido 2s o
3000 that I don't know I'm going to give them
3000 que no lo sé Se los voy a dar un
money that I have already contributed that the
dinero que yo ya he cotizado que ya me
Treasury has already taken from me Half what the hell am I
ha quitado Hacienda La mitad que [__]
going to give you but it's not only
te voy a dar pero es que ya no solamente
that I'm going to give a [ __ ] but how am
que le vaya a dar un [__] es que cómo
I going to go about returning money
me voy a poner yo a devolverle el dinero
to people the first thing How am I going to go about
a gente lo primero Cómo me voy a poner
returning money to people that
yo a devolverle el dinero a gente que
YouTube has taken their share The Treasury has
YouTube se ha llevado su parte Hacienda
taken their
se ha llevado su
share and that I'm not going to return you and
parte y que yo ya no te voy a devolver y
out suitable to a person who is being
fuera apte a una persona que está
sued three times that you are missing this
triplemente demandada que te falta este
year to receive another lawsuit
año por llegarte otra demanda más
and that you are declared in Rebellion or in other words I
y que estás declarada en Rebeldía o sea
am suing you that you have to
te estoy demandando que me tienes que
pay me what is asked of you in the lawsuit And
pagar lo que se te pide en la demanda Y
I am going to return it to you The money that
yo te voy a devolver a ti El dinero que
you have given here being a contributor to the
tú hayas dado aquí siendo aportador del
channel is that no no I don't understand in what
canal es que no no no entiendo en qué
head that idiot fits who are
cabeza cabe esa gilipo que están
repeating the  bad again and again
repitiendo los malitos una y otra vez
like all the [ __ ] they
como todas las gilipolleces que
repeat If a person here has become a
repiten Si una persona aquí se ha hecho
member has given super chat has given a visa
miembro ha dado super chat ha dado visum
no no no it will not be returned it can be
no no no se le va a devolver se le puede
returned on one occasion that
devolver en una ocasión que se haya
the woman has been mistaken as has happened
equivocado a la mujer como ha pasado
a few times but now I have
algunas veces pero que yo ahora un
money already declared that
dinero ya cotizado declarado que se ha
YouTube has taken its share that YouTube takes
llevado YouTube su parte que YouTube se
30 and the Treasury takes half
lleva el 30 y Hacienda me quita la mitad
of what's left We are
de lo que queda Estamos
crazy that I am going to take it out of my
locos que yo lo voy a [__] de mi
pocket to give it to you when the one who
bolsillo para dártelo cuando la que me
has to give me money is you who is being
tienes que dar dinero eres tú que estás
sued not me me Every nonsense I
demandada que no yo yo Cada tontería que
hear from the Monster Gang
escucho de de la de La Pandilla Monster
is getting bigger every day what
es cada día una tontería más gorda lo
Loli has to do is appear in person
que tiene que hacer Loli es personarte
at the lawsuit that is what you have to
en la demanda eso es lo que tienes que
do appear in person at the lawsuit Okay and go
hacer personarte en la demanda Vale y ir
to court that is what you have to
al juicio eso es lo que tienes que
do while I told you that it was not
hacer mientras te he dicho que no hacía
necessary okay But since you
falta vale Pero como te volviste a
offered again and I told you that ah that I offered again that's it I have already
ofrecer y te dije que ah que me volví a
added it that is already
ofrecer es eso ya lo he añadido eso ya
an
es un
addition yes the
añadido sí lo
bis bis bis eh
bis bis bis eh
Javi if it is ch  now about money
Javi si está ch ahora de dinero
Loli you should have thought better about the salaries
Loli haberte pensado mejor Los sueldos
that you've been giving and the things that you've been
que has ido dando y las cosas que tú
giving out there to people
hayas estado dando por ahí a la gente
that you don't even talk to now it's
con la que ahora ni te hables
probably worth thinking about it no
seguramente vale habértelo pensado no
what Damn I'm going to give you
que [__] Te voy a dar un
money money that's more than quoted more than
dinero dinero más que cotizado más que
spent in reality it
gastado en realidad
's the 5 that the reality is that the
son las 5 que la realidad es que el
phone is there that's why
teléfono está ahí por eso
B Ha that you didn't need that
B Ja eso que a ti no te hacía falta que
it was useless That that that's that's what
eso no servía para nada Eso eso eso es
and you don't that that already b b but
eso lo de y tú no que eso ya b b pero
the ones that were going to you the ones that were
los de que iban para ti los que
going friends of yours too
iban amigos tuyos también
the ones that were my friend Ivan that
los que iban que amigo mío el Iván que
the phone number that was used to
el número de teléfono que se utilizaba
find out about Ivan that he's part of the
enterar del Iván que forma parte del
team and he's part of the
equipo y forma parte de la
company are real things
empresa son cosas de verdad
such absurd insinuations and so so
insinuaciones tan absurdas y tan y tan
pathetic you know maybe he tells you this
patéticas sabes sea que te suelta esto
on the internet but then he doesn't have the
en internet pero luego no tiene malos
balls in a
[__] de un
trial he tells you this nonsense here
juicio te suelta estas tonterías aquí
to look for Pilar Vera to come and
para buscar que venga Pilar Vera y te
give you four emojis and then we don't have the
ponga cuatro emojis y luego no tenemos
balls to go to court we're not that
[__] de acudir al jugado no somos tan
brave then okay okay
valientes entonces vale
You stay you stay with  that it wasn't
vale Te quedas te quedas con que no iba
all for one, it's not that he kicked us out this
todo para uno no es nos ha botado este
now we need you this
ahora te Necesitamos este
Aha there's
Ahá hay la noticia que
the news that pissed do you remember record do you remember b b b that B Oh dolores beautiful beautiful Oh how well that channel has behaved with how well we have behaved B we want bisu B bisu can you imagine declaring it's that of course you imagine declaring this can you imagine she is declaring in the
esto os imagináis está declarando en el
trial I mean I think that what's going to happen she has already
juicio o sea yo creo que lo que va a ser
said
ya lo ha dicho
eh she has already said what's going to happen she
eh ella ha dicho ya lo que va a serc lo
has already said in several live shows she is not going
ha dicho ya en varios directos no se va
to appear in court and the sentence
a personar en el juicio y la condena
is for her payment that what she is going to
pores la paga eso lo que va a
do when she is convicted in her
hacer cuando esté condenada en el
live show she will say that it is a lie
directo suyo dirá que es mentira
Abi you have forgotten visum visum
Abi que se te ha olvidado visum visum
visum that you have told your entire
visum que tú le has dicho a toda tu
community that you can return it come on I
comunidad que puedes devolverlo venga
wish it for you for next year
para te lo deseo para el año que viene
that you don't lie to them so much don't lie to them at
que no les mientas tanto no les mientas
that level And if you have a man's word
a ese nivel Y si tienes palabra de
eh At least those who are in public
eh Por lo menos los que están en público
who are easy eh Hey
que son facilitos eh Ey
eh  It's not you who offered it, I
eh No eres tú el que lo ofrecía yo no
wasn't the one asking you for it, eh it's you, damn it, why do
era la que te lo te lo pido eh eres tú
n't you ask for it, he's been asking for it for two
[__] para no pedirlo lleva lleva dos
years, eh, things are a little bit
años pidiéndolo eh lleva está la cosilla
weak, eh They don't pay well anymore or
flojilla eh Ya no pagan bien o
what have you said on multiple occasions that you
qué has dicho en múltiples ocasiones qué
wanted to return it? Well, come on,
querías devolverlo Pues venga
guys, man,
vamos chicos
Ah look here is the
Ah mira aquí está el
c you start to slander
c te pones a difarme a
me when you have always been defended here
mí cuando aquí se te ha defendido
and it hasn't been for the money,
siempre y no ha sido por el dinero que
the money Ah if you want, give me your account
el dinero Ah si quieres me das tu cuenta
and I'll give it back to you, that's a
y te lo devuelvo eso eso es
lie, I'm just now about the money,
mentira yo es que ahora lo del dinero
that's a lie but I'm telling you the truth
eso es mentira pero te lo digo de verdad
if you want the money, give me your account and I'll
si quieres el dinero me das tu cuenta y
give it back to you, eh I don't know what, well no, no, I don't
te lo devuelvo eh No sé cu pues no no no
need it, okay, but you have
lo necesito vale pero que aquí se te ha
always been treated here Look, look, this is the living room of
siempre Mirar mirar esto es el salón de
my other house, man, Okay, then take
mi otra casa tío Bueno pues coge el
Wilson's stalker, okay, and cut this,
acosador de Wilson vale Y recorta este
click, I'll give it back to you, eh, yes,
click te lo devuelvo eh si
for the money, the money, now if you
por el dinero que el dinero ahora si
want, give me your account and I'll
quieres me das tu cuenta y te lo
give it back to you, eh And cut it here because
devuelvo eh Y lo corta aquí que él
when he got super sick A
cuando se habrá puesto super enfermo A
swallow a thousand straight to find This is
tragarse mil directo para encontrar Esto
worth it he will have seen the whole thing and when he
vale él habrá visto entero y cuando ha
saw this that to Loli saying that he does not
visto esto eso a la Loli diciendo que no
cut it from the clip Why Because he is a
la corta del clip Por qué Porque es un
stalker who clicks who
acosador que hace click que los
manipulates them you know trust yourself this This is
manipula sabes fíate tú esto Esto es
calmly Look at the entries I am
tranquilamente Mira las entradas estoy
fatter I
más gordete
have no other voice because of the
no tengo otra voz por el tema de la
breathing issue that is a
respiración eso es
lie I am that now the money thing
mentira yo es que ahora lo del dinero
that is a lie but I tell you it for
eso es mentira pero te lo digo lo lo por
three or four years of course here it is before
tres o cu años claro aquí es antes de
everything happens but obviously I am
que pase todo pero evidentemente yo
not going to tell this lady
luego no le voy a decir a esta señora
that I am going to return anything I
que le voy a devolver nada Esto se lo
told her this at this moment because a lady
dije en este momento porque una señora
who had donated four or five times
que había donado cuatro o cinco veces
here I don't know how many it would have to be seen but we
aquí no sé cuántas habría que verlo pero
were talking maybe 300 500
estábamos hablando a lo mejor de 300 500
euros in the previous weeks okay already
eur en las semanas anteriores vale ya
she lowered her head in the call
ella ahí agachó la cabeza en la llamada
oh oh well yes it is true it is that I have
ay ay bueno sí es verdad es que me he
heated up with you I have put you green
calentado contigo te he puesto verde por
there blah blah you know and that's it and
ahí patatín patatán sabes y ya está y
there it stayed Aha that then later she
ahí se quedó Aha que luego luego ella
reappeared around here when when
volvió a aparecer por aquí cuando cuando
I started my program with Marina that my
empecé yo mi programa con Marina que mi
program with  Marina, I didn't live in this
programa con Marina yo no vivía en esta
house anymore, I remember perfectly well
casa ya yo me acuerdo perfectamente de
me talking to Marina here standing on the
yo hablando con Marina aquí de pie por
phone when we agreed on the program,
teléfono cuando acordamos el el programa
okay, here in this house, the
vale aquí en esta casa ya empezó el
program with Marina and Loli started two or
programa con Marina y y Loli a los dos o
three, two or three years later, the program Loli was
tres a los dos o tres programa Loli fue
when she appeared, you have it on TR
cuando apareció eso lo tenéis en en TR
alc, you can
alc lo podéis
find it two or three years later,
encontrar a los dos o tres programas
Loli began to appear And that's when she
Loli empezó a aparecer Y fue cuando
began to donate, the number of times that Loli donated, more than the number of times she had been donating,
empezó a donar las veces que más que más
well, a couple of months or three, no, no, it
bien Un par de meses o tres no más claro
seems like here, this lady, a little more,
que parece aquí que esta señora poco más
and she paid us the salary, no, no,
y nos pagaba a nosotros el suerdo no no
he must have paid it somewhere else here,
el lo habrá pagado en otro sitio aquí
Loli, what she has paid here, like this, what she has
Loli lo lo que ha pagado aquí así lo que
donated, the number of times she has
ha donado las veces que ha
donated has been two or three
donado han sido dos o tres
months and it is one and they are amounts that I have
meses y es una y son cantidades que yo
not noticed in her salary, the truth is, it
no las he notado en el suerdo la verdad
is not something that is a difference,
no es una cosa que sea una diferencia de
Uy, you can see that now we have Loli, me
Uy se nota que ahora tenemos a Loli me
[Music] do you
[Música]
understand, look at the program
entiendes mira el programa
with the program with
con el programa con
Marina, the first program with Marina
Marina el primer programa con Marina
When is Joe, I don't know if Joe is there,
Cuándo es Joe no sé si está Joe por ahí
Joe knows the
que Joe sabe la
date, well  the first program that
fecha pues el el primer programa que
was with
fuera con
Marina Lolid Don't no from the second
marina lolid Don no a partir del segundo
third program I think more or less
tercer programa yo creo que más o menos
around there she appeared okay well maybe
por ahí apareció vale bueno a lo mejor
two or three weeks okay maybe in
dos o tres semanas vale a lo mejor a las
two or three weeks and it ends Loli
dos o tres semanas y termina Loli
ends in the summer when she gets the sack the
termina en verano cuando la trinca la
pppa that I remember I who are fat
pppa que me acuerdo Yo que los gordos
I was in Portugal do you remember that
estaba yo en Portugal os acordáis que
I was in Portugal and that thing with
estaba yo en Portugal y pasó aquello de
Pilar happened I don't know
Pilar no sé
what I mean there you have the months
qué O sea ahí tenéis ustedes los meses
that she has donated that of course It seems that this
que ha donado que claro Parece que esta
lady has supported us for 2 years
señora nos ha mantenido durante 2 años
no no no no this lady was here
no no no no esta señora estuvo aquí
donating what 3
donando qué 3
months in November 22 Look J
meses en noviembre del 22 Mira dice J
Hunter says that Marina starts on
Hunter que empieza Marina el 22 de
November 22, 22 Okay so put in
noviembre del 22 Vale pues ponte que a
how many weeks will Loli appear okay
las cuantas semanas aparecerá Loli vale
half a year at the most which will be less
medio año como muchísimo que será menos
okay but
vale pero
c or months was Loli on this
c o se meses estuvo Loli en este
channel like
canal como
a lot well wait like a lot I'm
muchísimo bueno espérate como muchísimo
going to tell you until when I'm going to
te voy a decir hasta cuándo te voy a
tell you until when Marina snal Marta
decir hasta cuándo Marina snal Marta
riesco February
riesco febrero del
23 Loli was here Loli ha was here
23 Loli estuvo aquí Loli ha estaba aquí
two months Joe Look Loli ha was here
dos meses Joe Mira Loli ha estaba aquí
two months
dos meses
donating damn no  I knew it had been
donando ostia no sabía que había estado
so
tan
unclear, I was saying like
poco claro yoos estaba diciendo como
summer because I remember that Pilar's thing
mucho verano porque me acuerdo que lo de
was in summer when I was at the
Pilar fue en verano que estaba yo en la
beach, you know, the
playa sabes en
same, but no, no, no, in February, this
igual pero no no no en febrero aquí este
was the live broadcast of the
fue el directo de la
discord. Of course, in February, two or three
discordia Claro en febrero dos o tres
months, Loli was here donating, and she
meses estuvo aquí donando la Loli y me
's telling me that I have to give it back, I
está diciendo que le tengo devolver te
'm going to give it back to you.
voy a devolver